{
    "subject": "resource/John_C._McManus",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "McManus",
    "human_readable": "The surname of John C. McManus is McManus.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870883822441101,
            "question": "What is the surname of John C. McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8929609060287476,
            "question": "Is 'McManus' a common surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8667196035385132,
            "question": "Are there any notable families with the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8642272353172302,
            "question": "What is the meaning behind the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621584177017212,
            "question": "Are there any historical figures with the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8548924326896667,
            "question": "What are some possible origins of the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8418870568275452,
            "question": "What are some potential nicknames associated with the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772510290145874,
            "question": "Can you provide some examples of famous people with the surname McManus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7611839771270752,
            "question": "How common is the surname McManus in different countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.619935929775238,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the name 'McManus' and Irish culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of John C. McManus is McManus.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1924_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How common is the surname McManus in different countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1924_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide some examples of famous people with the surname McManus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1924_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential nicknames associated with the surname McManus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1924_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1924_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the surname McManus, confirming that it is indeed the surname of individuals like John C. McManus, as mentioned in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}